ratzillacosme.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to RatzillaCosme.com.  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that RatzillaCosme.com collects, and the ways in which RatzillaCosme.com uses that personal information.

**Personal Information Collection**

RatzillaCosme.com may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services
  * any other information that you send to RatzillaCosme.com.

**Using Personal Information**

RatzillaCosme.com may use your personal information to:

  * personalize the website for you
  * enable your access to and use of the website services
  * publish information about you on the website (only with your prior approval)

Where RatzillaCosme.com discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, RatzillaCosme.com may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing Your Data**

RatzillaCosme.com will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

RatzillaCosme.com does not store personal information you provide.

**Cross-Border Data Transfers**

Information that RatzillaCosme.com collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which RatzillaCosme.com operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating This Statement**

RatzillaCosme.com may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other Websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

RatzillaCosme.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Credit**

The document above was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.contractology.com](http://www.contractology.com/).

**Log Files**  
Like many other sites, RatzillaCosme.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RatzillaCosme.com.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to RatzillaCosme.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

**Other Cookies**

Some of RatzillaCosme.com’s advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on the site. Advertising partners include but not limited to Google AdSense, Rakuten, and Amazon.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on RatzillaCosme.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

RatzillaCosme.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. RatzillaCosme.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective [websites](http://bit.ly/2hPhQVS).
